<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>David Murphy</title>
    <link>https://davidmurphy.netlify.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on David Murphy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>David Murphy</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 19:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://davidmurphy.netlify.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ruby On Rails Complete</title>
      <link>https://davidmurphy.netlify.com/blog/ruby-on-rails-completed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 19:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidmurphy.netlify.com/blog/ruby-on-rails-completed/</guid>
      <description>I finally finished the tutorial I was following for Ruby on Rails. I really had a lot of fun following along and learned a lot along the way. Stuff like how important attention to detail really is in development, asking questions isn&amp;rsquo;t ever frowned upon, and how good it felt to release it. Releasing my first web application is actually really exciting and I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to deploy it.
I feel extremely accomplished with all of this, and I can honestly see how far I&amp;rsquo;ve come in such a quick time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Give Up!</title>
      <link>https://davidmurphy.netlify.com/blog/dont-give-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 21:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidmurphy.netlify.com/blog/dont-give-up/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, if there has been anything I&amp;rsquo;ve taken away from working with my friend Alex to improve my developing skills and to actually become a developer is to not give up. Why? When I started I couldn&amp;rsquo;t even tell you what a class was, now I can tell you with confidence it is a type of method. If I gave up I would of never made my first project, my website, or felt I was actually cut out for this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Ruby Gem</title>
      <link>https://davidmurphy.netlify.com/blog/my-first-ruby-gem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 23:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidmurphy.netlify.com/blog/my-first-ruby-gem/</guid>
      <description>Today someone came to me on ruby on rails link slack and told me I should try to turn google-cli into a Ruby Gem. He told me to start with a tutorial. During this tutorial I learned that Ruby Gem was already on my computer. Though with a few tries I finally got it!
All in all, my main take away for this was realizing how far along I&amp;rsquo;ve come, but it&amp;rsquo;s made me realize I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;m quite ready to make my own executeable gem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Constants</title>
      <link>https://davidmurphy.netlify.com/blog/constant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 14:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidmurphy.netlify.com/blog/constant/</guid>
      <description>So today I got into the 3rd unit I did for excercism, it was called Gigasecond. So I did struggle with a few things but I&amp;rsquo;m going to focus on the main problem I had, which was methods. My biggest struggle was and has been up until now figuring out what to do for a method. I talked to some people in the Ruby On Rails chat that I&amp;rsquo;m in and realized there are two seperate types of methods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>google-cli</title>
      <link>https://davidmurphy.netlify.com/project/google-cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 22:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidmurphy.netlify.com/project/google-cli/</guid>
      <description> google-cli google-cli was the first project I ever completed. It is a command line interface for google searches. I decided to make it for faster searches while coding.
This is how it is used:
$ google What is the answer to the ultimate question of life, the universe, and everything\?  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://davidmurphy.netlify.com/blog/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 21:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidmurphy.netlify.com/blog/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>This is my first post, on my first website, on my first ever blog. Today I decided with my mentor to make my first site, following the creation of my project google-cli. I created my website using Hugo&amp;rsquo;s quick start guide. I feel like throughout the past few days I have learned a lot and it&amp;rsquo;s finally starting to show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://davidmurphy.netlify.com/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidmurphy.netlify.com/page/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me Hey, I&amp;rsquo;m David Murphy! I am currently learning how to develop in Ruby along with other developer skills such as navigating the linux terminal, using git, and roughly following test driven development practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://davidmurphy.netlify.com/page/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidmurphy.netlify.com/page/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Information Email: david.ryan.kroncke@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Time Seeing Ruby On Rails</title>
      <link>https://davidmurphy.netlify.com/blog/first-time-seeing-ror/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidmurphy.netlify.com/blog/first-time-seeing-ror/</guid>
      <description>Unfortunately today I got sent home early from work because I was sick, but the plus side is I got play around with Ruby on Rails today! I was honestly surprised by how easy it was to follow along and understand the tutorial I used for RoR. I definitely see a huge use to RoR for new developers as my self for not only organization but speed efficiency as well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>